Office for Technology Licensing and Industry Collaboration Records UA060
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Patent files, 1987 -- 2017; UA060.002; 7.0 Linear Feet
  - Kaplan, David - T001219 - European Union Patent No. 1558444 - Japan Patent No. 5855151, 2015 -- 2016; UA060.000186; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Kaplan, David - T001233 - US Patent No. 9,132,197 B2, 2015; UA060.000187; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Kaplan, David - T001239 - US Patent No. 9,539,362 B2, 2017; UA060.000188; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Kaplan, David - T001255 - US Patent No. 9,084,840 B2 - Canada Patent No. 2, 562, 415, 2015; UA060.000189; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Kaplan, Daivd - T001274 - Japan Patent No. 5941081, 2016; UA060.000190; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Kaplan, David - T001430 - European Union Patent No. 2650112, 2016; UA060.000191; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Kaplan, David - T001435 - Canada Patent No. 2704304 - European Union Patent No. 2107964, 2015 -- 2016; UA060.000192; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Kaplan, David - T001462 - European Union Patent No. 2129772 - Japan Patent No. 5970497 - US Patent No. 9,102,916 B2, 2015 -- 2016; UA060.000193; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Kaplan, David - T001463 - Mexico Patent No. 330744, 2015; UA060.000194; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Kaplan, David - T001489 - US Patent No. 9,504,575 B2, 2016; UA060.000195; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Kaplan, David - T001621 - European Union Patent No. 2483460, 2015; UA060.000196; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Kaplan, David - T001696 - US Patent No. 8,986,380 B2, 2015; UA060.000197; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Kaplan, David - T001713 - China Patent No. ZL201180061175.8 - Japan Patent No. 5937092, 2016; UA060.000198; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Kluge, Jon - T001463 - European Union Patent No. 2211876, 2014; UA060.000199; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Kumar-Singh, Rajendra - T001477 - US Patent No. 8,778,886 B2, 2014; UA060.000200; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Kumar-Singh, Rajendra - T001690 - US Patent No. 8,877,896 B2, 2014; UA060.000201; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Leisk, Gary - T001789 - US Patent No. 9,492,504 B2, 2016; UA060.000202; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Lo, Tim Jia-Chiang - T001621 - US Patent No. 9,074,302 B2, 2015; UA060.000203; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Omenetto, Fiorenzo - T001430 - Canada Patent No. 2,704,769, 2016; UA060.000204; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Omenetto, Fiorenzo - T001614 - US Patent No. 9.016,875 B2, 2015; UA060.000205; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Omenetto, Fiorenzo - T001623 - US Patent No. 9,142,787 B2, 2015; UA060.000206; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Omenetto, Fiorenzo - T001645 - European Union Patent No. 2559101, 2016; UA060.000207; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Omenetto, Fiorenzo - T001706 - US Patent No. 9,517,357 B2, 2016; UA060.000208; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Panetta, Karen - T001763 - US Patent No. 9,299,130 B2, 2016; UA060.000209; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Panetta, Karen - T001976 - US Patent No. 9,396,531 B2, 2016; UA060.000210; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Panjwani, Noorjahan - T001226 - Canada Patent No. 2,604,583 - China Patent No. ZL200680009189.4 - European Union Patent No. 1874337 - Korea Patent No. 10-1589742, 2014 -- 2016; UA060.000211; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Pirie, Chris - T001682 - US Patent No. 8,926,094 B2, 2015; UA060.000212; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Quek, Shu Qing - T001736 - US Patent No. 9,404,479 B2, 2016; UA060.000213; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Schwob, James - T001754 - US Patent No. 9,080,172 B2, 2015; UA060.000214; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Shoemaker, Charles - T001452 - US Patent No. 8,865,169 B2, 2014; UA060.000215; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Shoemaker, Charles - T001737 - US Patent No. 9,023,352 B2, 2015; UA060.000216; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Sonkusale, Sameer - T001549 - US Patent No. 9,459,375 B2, 2016; UA060.000217; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Tzipori, Saul - T001479 - US Patent No. 8,614,083 B2 - US Patent No. 9,522,350 B2, 2013 -- 2016; UA060.000218; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Vepari, Charu - T001332 - US Patent No. 9,290,579 B2, 2016; UA060.000219; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Vu, Mai - T001943 - US Patent No. 9,503,170 B2, 2016; UA060.000220; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Walt, David - T001388 - US Patent No. 8,932,869 B2, 2015; UA060.000221; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Walt, David - T001395 - Canada Patent No. 2,643,993 - Canada Patent No. 2,734,029 - European Union Patent No. 1996717 - European Union Patent No. 2201374 - European Union Patent No. 2538220 - US Patent No. 9,395,359 B2, 2014 -- 2016; UA060.000222; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Wang, Xiaqin - T001463 - Canada Patent No. 2,688,431 - US Patent No. 9,254,333 B2, 2016; UA060.000223; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Additional accessions, UA060.000160
  - The Office of Technology Licensing and Industry Collaboration, 1992 -- 1997; UA143-001 (Box 1)